Last time on Naomi...
Every superhero has an
origin story and this is mine.
What's going on?
Annabelle says there's a
stunt happening in the square.
Something happened to me
during the Superman thing.
Then I went to the woods
and found some kind of disc.
It can be hard once you realize
you're not like everyone else.
Stay back!
You were there
on the day I was adopted.
Who... Who are you?
Still asking the wrong question.
What is the question?
Who am I?
I don't know who you are.
Not exactly.
But I know that it all started
March 14th, 2004,
when I saw the light in the sky.
That's when I first sensed it.
Sensed what?
You.
What does that mean?
There are invisible
vibrations all around us.
In the air, in the water,
the trees.
People like us
have a unique
vibrational signature.
Think of it like
a, uh, fingerprint.
My wings give me
the ability to sense it.
Your wings,
because you have wings.
They're a part of me,
made from a rare metal
found on...
my home planet.
Your home planet?
Thanagar.
Thanagar...
Right.
But if you're from another
planet, that would mean...
I'm not human.
And if your, if your special wings
could sense me, that would mean...
You're not human either.
Okay.
This isn't real.
I'm having a very
bad dream right now
and I just need to wake up.
Just wake up Naomi,
just wake up, just wake up.
Sometimes when I'm stressed, I, uh...
I do some deep breathing.
I think I'll stick with the
straight-up panic attack.
I know it's a lot.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
You don't just blow up
someone's life for no reason.
Your abilities seemed dormant.
You seemed...
happy.
I think that's enough
for tonight.
You should go home
and get some rest.
I'm pretty sure I'm never
gonna sleep again,
and plus, I have like a
million more questions.
I know,
and I'll do my best
to answer them.
I promise.
Tomorrow.
Please.
You just told me I'm an
alien from outer space.
No disrespect, but am I really
just supposed to believe you?
No.
I'll prove it.
I know my birth parents
died in a crash...
but what kind?
Was it a car or a plane
or a bus?
We don't know, pumpkin.
You know we don't know.
We've talked about this
dozens of times.
Baby, what's going on?
Nothing.
I guess I've just been
thinking about it,
lately, that's all.
That's completely normal.
You're getting older and
it's natural to want answers.
We wish we had them, but
you know everything we know.
But is there anything else?
Like what town, or was
anyone else there?
All the agency would tell us is that
it was on the East Coast. It was a...
It was a closed adoption.
But didn't it bother you?
Not knowing who I really am
or where I actually came from?
None of that mattered to us.
It still doesn't.
We know who you are.
You're our daughter.
Our miracle.
I better...
start getting ready.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, Dad.
We're your parents.
Keeping you safe
is basically our entire job.
So it's...
hard to accept that we can't
keep you safe from everything.
But what I can promise
is that we love you
and we are here for you.
I know that, Dad.
I really do.
Good.
Better get to school.
♪ I am not a woman I'm a god ♪
♪ I am not a martyr
I'm a problem ♪
♪ I am not a legend
I'm a fraud ♪
♪ Keep your heart
'Cause I already ♪
♪ Every day I've got a smile
Where my frown goes ♪
♪ A couple bodies in the garden
Where the grass grows ♪
♪ I take 'em with me
To the grave in a suitcase ♪
♪ Maybe I could be A different
human In a new place ♪
♪ Oh
♪ I just wanna feel something
Tell me where to go ♪
♪ 'Cause everybody knows
Something I don't wanna know ♪
♪ So I'll stay right here
'Cause I'm better all alone ♪
♪ I'm better all alone
♪ I am not a woman I'm a god ♪
♪ I am not a martyr
I'm a problem ♪
♪ I am not a legend
I'm a fraud ♪
♪ Keep your heart
'Cause I already got one ♪
♪ I am not a woman I'm a god ♪
♪ I am not a martyr
I'm a problem ♪
♪ I am not a legend
I'm a fraud ♪
Whoa!
Sorry, I thought you might, uh,
want some caffeine
after our late night expedition.
That's really nice, thanks.
I'm sorry we didn't find that disc
you were looking for at Zumbado's.
Oh! That's okay.
Uh... I mean, it was fun though.
Hanging out with you
is always fun, actually, uh,
and, I mean, it got me thinking.
I was wondering if maybe you wanted
to, um, hang out this weekend? Or...
Maybe without the trespassing.
We could try that new,
uh, pizza place.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Pizza sounds good.
Really?
Okay, great, okay, wow, okay!
All right, text me later?
Okay, yes,
I'll... I'll text you later.
Thanks for this!
You're welcome.
Dee?
Naomi.
You made it.
I don't really like heights.
Did you know
that the first bridges were built
by the people of ancient Egypt?
No machinery.
Just chisels and stones
with their own two hands.
Humans have the capacity
to do incredible things.
What are we doing here?
Jumping.
Hold up, you're serious?
You asked for proof.
Here it is.
You'll defy gravity.
You won't even make a splash.
You won't get hurt.
That's easy for you to say.
You have wings.
True.
Have you ever had a broken bone?
Stitches?
Any injuries at all?
Sure.
When?
You've never been injured...
because you're not like
everyone else.
Besides, if I'm wrong,
what's the worst
that can happen?
You make a big splash,
break your foot.
That sounds pretty bad.
You're afraid.
You just told me
to jump off a bridge.
What happened to you
in the woods,
the lights going out in my shop,
that was all you.
The sooner you accept that,
the safer you'll be.
Safe from what?
Your world has
fundamentally changed
and I doubt I'm
the only one who's noticed.
We need to get you ready.
It's impossible.
Superman once told me,
impossible is relative.
Superman?
I fought with him in a war
a long time ago.
He is real, Naomi.
No.
I'm sorry, but no.
Superheroes are not real.
Aliens are not real.
Your wings must have been some kind
of harness or machine or something.
And the light that you saw in the sky
was probably a meteor or satellite.
I'm gonna find the crash site and figure
out what really happened that day.
You're not ready.
To accept that I'm an alien
from outer space? No.
No, I'm not.
Dee!
Finding the crash site
won't change the truth, Naomi.
This is real,
whether you believe it or not.
Mrs. M! Hi! Is that a new top?
Loving that color on you.
Thanks, honey.
I went shopping last week.
You were right, I can pull off pastels.
Want a smoothie?
You know I do.
Naomi sent me a soft 911.
It's one step down from an
actual medical emergency.
It includes, but is not
limited to, romantic emergency,
school emergency, snack
emergency, fashion emergency.
Good to know.
She's working
on a school project.
It's a little...
intense in there.
♪ I'm true to my squad
♪ I'm true to my dead ones Who
walk with me Know when I'm flawed ♪
♪ I'm true to my squad
♪ True to the people who see me
Right through the facade ♪
You know, I always thought
we'd be cute, little old ladies
before we went full
conspiracy theorist.
Good, you're here.
Uh, can you come
help me with this?
What's going on here, babe?
It's a topographic map
of Port Oswego.
It's pretty dope. It shows water,
elevation, surface features.
No, um, what's going on here?
There was a UFO sighting back
in Port Oswego in 2004.
And we're hunting
aliens because...
We're not. That's the point.
UFO doesn't mean aliens. It
means unidentified flying object.
So, I'm trying to identify it.
Right. Weren't we on a disc
mission, like, five minutes ago?
This is more important.
There've been a lot of UFO sightings
in Port Oswego, like, a lot.
Did you know that?
Can't say that I did.
A lot of people thought that the March
14th UFO landed in Red River Forest.
But I compared the wind reports
to an article about soil testing
and my theory is that it landed
somewhere around Falls Creek.
I want to go look around.
Mom said that
I can borrow the car.
March 14th, 2004?
As in the day you were adopted.
I think it was a secret military drone
and that's why no one came forward.
- Apparently the government was running this...
- Naomi!
You are telling me,
on the day you were adopted,
way on the others side of the country, there
was a UFO sighting here in Port Oswego...
where you now live.
Smoothie time.
Fresh fruits and vitamin C
coming your way.
- Thanks, Mom.
- You're the best, Mrs. M.
Naomi, I just got
a call from Dad.
He's stuck at work so you won't
be able to use the car tonight.
Don't worry.
I happen to know somebody
else who loves UFOs.
No offense, hon, but will this
thing even make it to Falls Creek?
Shh. You'll hurt her feelings.
Who wants snacks?
Ooh, now it's a road trip.
- You got any gummy bears in there?
- Ew!
Thank you.
You wanted to see me, sir?
I did. Come on in, Major.
Have a seat.
Very impressive resume, Major.
Counterintelligence analyst
for the DOD,
on-the-ground experience
in several countries.
Thank you, sir.
You're aware of the incident that happened
a few days ago in the town square.
The Superman publicity stunt?
We're not sure what it was.
All we know is that it was an
unidentified flying object near our base.
I thought the owner of the tattoo
shop admitted to planning it.
He did. But we think that
there is more to the story.
Our team found this during a
sweep of the Red River Forest
near the alleged landing site.
Our lab techs have had it
for the last couple of days.
We can't break it, burn it, blow it up.
It's virtually indestructible.
Sounds like boron carbide or maybe
some other kind of synthetic.
That's what I thought.
But the technology
is far more advanced.
It's unlike anything
we've ever seen.
And you think it has something
to do with the Superman incident?
I don't know what to think.
Why would Dee say
he planned it if he didn't?
What does he have
to do with this?
That's what I need you
to find out.
I am definitely not wearing
the right shoes for this.
Speaking of shoes, Naomi,
let's talk about what pair you're
gonna wear on your date with Anthony.
- What?
- My first thought is your blue high tops
but your Chucks could be
super cute too. I mean...
No, what do you mean, date?
Was Anthony not supposed
to tell me?
I think he was just excited.
We're having pizza like we do
all the time. It's not a date.
It's not a date!
So much internal cringe, babe.
What's in the suitcase?
My gear.
Every good UFO investigator
has gear.
He thinks aliens are real.
Really?
Definitely.
It's pretty much
a mathematical certainty.
But there's never been
any proof that they exist.
There's never been
any proof that they don't.
What exactly are we looking for?
I mean, 16 years is a long time.
Debris or any other
evidence of a crash.
Trees that are broken.
Newer growth.
Scorch marks or burns.
There could also be
trace elements.
Like radiation or chemicals.
I'm good.
Latex isn't really my color.
Let's get started.
♪ You know you wanna
I should have worn gloves.
This sap is everywhere.
It's bigleaf maple.
Very tasty on pancakes,
but very messy.
Naomi?
Naomi.
Naomi!
Are you okay?
I could hear it, Annabelle.
Hear what?
Everything.
Okay.
Don't freak out.
See, when someone says that, it means
you definitely should be freaking out.
Are you moving?
After we broke into Zumbado's,
I went to see Dee and...
things got weird.
He sprouted these, like, actual
metal wings and then he told me that
he's an alien from outer space and that he
thinks that I too am an alien from outer space.
Oh, and he also said
that Superman is real.
Annabelle, please say something.
I am literally speechless.
It's never happened
to me before.
OMG, babe! Are you a superhero?
No! No.
Suddenly the whole UFO thing
makes so much more sense...
Wait, why are we trying to
prove you're not a superhero?
Aliens aren't real.
Superheroes aren't real.
Right?
But what if they are?
If you could be any character from
Greek mythology, who would you be?
What?
It's, uh, one of my questions.
For our project?
Here's my list.
Mine's not done yet. I'm sorry.
I'd be Zeus.
He has like, a ton of powers,
which make him the coolest.
Maybe having all those powers
wasn't actually that fun.
Or maybe Zeus wished that he could just
be regular god without all the pressure.
Or maybe he didn't want
to be a god at all.
What is happening right now?
Nothing.
Can you come by after soccer
to work on our project?
Sure.
Do you think your mom
would make me a smoothie?
Totally. Yesterday's had
fresh coconut.
The woman is a visionary.
Thanks for this.
Anytime.
All these trees
look exactly the same.
What are we hoping to see here?
Patterns, markings, anything we
might have missed at the site.
Wait, is this Falls Creek?
I can't believe you guys went there.
Because of Steve O'Brien?
Since you are looking into the
2004 sighting, I assumed you knew.
It's a Port Oswego urban legend.
Let's definitely tell horror
stories in an actual dark room.
So, Steve is this local guy
who is obsessed with UFOs.
And in 2004 he would have been a
junior or senior in high school.
He and some friends went into the
woods to look for the crash site.
And apparently some weird stuff
started to happen at Falls Creek.
What kind of weird stuff?
It depends on who you ask.
Some people think he saw
the ghosts of dead loggers
and other people claim
he saw Bigfoot.
Lot of people just think he was
high with his friends. But, uh...
After he came back from the woods,
Steve refused to talk about it.
Where is he now?
He still lives in Port Oswego.
This is where Steve lives?
Was really expecting more of
a cabin in the woods vibe,
It's a lot less true crime
and more mommy blogger.
Anthony, you got tall.
Thanks for making the time to see us, Mr.
O'Brien.
Sure, sure.
How's your dad these days?
Ah, my father's good, sir.
Work's just a little slow.
Uh, my dad and Mr. O'Brien have done
some logging jobs back in the day.
So, what can I do for you?
Anthony said something
about a school project.
It's about the UFO back in 2004.
I'm not really
into UFOs any more.
Because of what happened
in 2004?
It's less about what happened
and more about what I wanted
for my life.
I realized I could keep
being the strange UFO guy
or I could fit in with
everyone else, be normal.
What happened back then?
I... I don't like
to talk about it.
Please.
It's important.
Um, I can't really explain it.
I just...
I feel like I'm meant
to solve this.
I remember that feeling.
I was skateboarding
in the square
when I saw the light that day.
So me and a couple of my friends
decided to try
and find the crash site.
We were almost to the mill
when things started to happen.
The woods
started to feel... alive.
We heard voices.
Lots of... Lots of voices.
We never saw
anyone else out there.
What happened when
you got to the mill?
We never made it inside.
We were almost there.
We heard this...
horrible noise.
And then I saw this
really bright light...
and that's all
I can remember before.
Before what?
Um, I was somehow back at the car
and I have no idea how I got there.
We didn't see a mill
at Falls Creek.
- Falls Creek?
- The crash site.
The UFO didn't land at Falls Creek.
We were a few miles away.
We've been looking
in the wrong place.
We have to find that mill.
No, thank you.
Those voices Steve heard must have been
someone trying to cover up the crash.
Maybe the military
or someone else.
Jacob, you're with me, right?
Definitely.
Well, not technically.
I'm with you in spirit.
My backlog of homework is
getting pretty serious.
Same.
Me, too.
No, we have to solve this!
I thought we were
just having fun.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for all your help.
We should pack this up.
I'll go get some boxes.
Is this a safe space?
I'm sorry for snapping at you.
I know that weird stuff
is happening to me, but,
aliens, superheroes.
It's crazy, right?
I don't know, babe.
I mean, yes, it seems crazy,
maybe even impossible, but...
I mean, people used to think
the Earth was flat.
Doctors used to not wash their hands
before surgery, which is very gross.
We didn't even know
gravity was a thing.
Even if you're right,
even if there are...
aliens and superheroes,
why does it have to be me?
What do you mean?
I'm adopted. I was always moving
around because of my dad's job.
Most of the time I was the only Black
girl in my town or in my school.
My whole life has been about being
different and now I'm supposed to...
accept the fact that I'm literally
an alien from outer space.
I just want to be normal.
You are a lot of things, babe,
but normal is not one of them.
You, Naomi McDuffie,
are exceptional.
I'm pretty sure you're biased.
No, it's a fact.
So you know the Serenity Prayer?
"May I be granted the serenity to
accept the things I cannot change,"
the courage to change
the things I can,
"and the wisdom to know
the difference."
I think what it means is that
there's some things in life we
can't change and that's okay.
I'm scared, Annabelle.
I know.
And that's okay too.
But denying something
doesn't make it any less real.
Maybe accepting it is the first
step towards making it less scary.
More cheese. A little more.
A little more.
Perfect. You're a natural.
The secret to Mom's pasta
is ninety percent cheese.
She's right.
Speaking of, I left
a grocery bag in the car.
Naomi, take these bowls
to your friends.
You're still here.
We all are.
If this UFO hunt is important
to you, it's important to us.
Also, I couldn't say no to
Mrs. McDuffie's pasta, so...
Hope I'm not interrupting.
Nathan, what are you doing here?
Your mom let me in.
What's he doing here?
You know, I'm standing
right here.
Could you, um, take these
bowls to Jacob and Annabelle?
What are you doing here?
Seriously?
You told me to come by
after soccer practice.
Oh, our project.
You keep forgetting
about our project.
You forgot I was coming over.
And then when I show up,
all these people are here.
Anthony's here?
That's pretty not cool.
I know.
I'm sorry. I can explain.
All right.
Hey, what's going on
with you, for real?
Nothing.
I just have a lot on my mind,
that's all.
Is this about Dee?
What?
When we went to see him the
other day, you seemed upset.
I know we're not together,
but...
I'm still your friend.
You can talk to me.
Naomi, you need to
come see this.
Steve said the mill
was close to the creek,
but none of these are
within a ten-mile radius.
Maybe Steve was wrong.
These are the only operational
mills near Falls Creek.
This is a Pacific Logging map.
It lists all the mills.
Pacific #42
decommissioned in 1989,
three miles away from the creek.
I feel like I, uh, missed a lot.
We'll catch you up on the way.
I guess homework
will have to wait.
Is it just me, or is this
car getting a little crowded?
Uh-oh.
I knew this car was
living on borrowed time.
Time to call AAA?
I have a better idea.
You guys are really
bad at hitchhiking.
Thanks for coming, Lourdes.
You know I'm always happy
to get a text from you.
We have to walk
the rest of the way.
It's about a mile.
This is the beginning of
literally every horror movie.
What the hell is this?
These markings were on the disc.
Someone's coming.
Guys, we have to go.
I know you're here, Naomi.
And you brought your friends.
Did you know someone
broke into my dealership?
That's called
criminal trespassing.
Police came by, asked if I had
any idea who might have done it.
I'm still deciding
on what to tell them.
You all must really care about Naomi
to put yourselves in harm's way.
You can leave now, except Naomi.
- No way.
- Hell no!
If he thinks we're leaving you
here, he's crazier than we thought.
If I stay,
will my friends be safe?
I give you my word.
That does not
make me feel better.
We are not leaving you
alone with a criminal
who's doing creepy things
inside of a creepy mill.
Annabelle, I'll be fine.
Remember? Zeus.
Fine. If Naomi says to go,
we should go.
We have to trust her.
We'll be right outside.
Aim for his eyes.
- Okay?
- Okay.
What do you want?
Why did you follow me here?
I want you to stay out of this
before you get hurt.
Impressive. Much more focused
than your display in the woods.
Using those will
get you into trouble.
What happened here
on March 14th?
Nothing to do with you.
You're lying.
If you're not gonna
believe me, then why ask?
What is this place?
What are those markings?
Tell me what's...
Stop messing with things
that you don't understand.
Go, and don't ever
come back here.
Anthony, wait up.
Thanks again, Lourdes.
Literally, anytime.
Hey! Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I think Zumbado was just trying
to scare us or something.
Mission accomplished.
What was he even doing there? Was
that payback for the break-in?
I don't know.
Well... Hey, about that pizza...
I...
You changed your mind.
I didn't know you wanted
to get pizza like that.
Oh...
This is awkward.
No, no, I don't want it to be.
I just have a lot going on,
so for right now,
could we just stay friends?
Yeah. Yeah, of course. I get it.
No, I don't think you do.
I'm not saying no, Anthony,
I'm just saying not right now.
I can live with that.
What is going on here?
Naomi is doing a school project.
I tracked down
that actor Dee hired,
but all I got was
a full voice mailbox.
So it's a dead end?
It's feeling like it.
Commander Steel wants
to see me first thing.
He said he has
something to tell me.
Do you agree with him?
Is Dee some kind of threat?
I don't know if he's a threat,
but he's definitely
hiding something.
Why are you helping me?
You didn't have to
tell me the truth.
Wouldn't it have just been
easier for you to stay quiet?
I know what it feels like to
be different and not know why.
I really wanted you to be wrong.
I know.
I told myself that if I could just prove
that something else happened on March 14th,
something real,
that things could just go back
to the way that they were,
before Superman,
before all of this.
Now I know I can't.
I don't know
what is happening to me.
All I know is that
it is happening.
And how do you feel?
Scared, confused, excited.
Dee, I think I have powers.
Yes, and they're actually
pretty great,
once you get used to them.
Could you introduce me
to Superman?
Um... Maybe one day.
Thank you for
telling me the truth.
You're welcome.
That energy thing,
it happened again,
like it did in the woods
and in here with the lights.
But this time,
I meant to cause it.
But I couldn't control it.
I think I can help with that.
Welcome to the team, Major.
Sir, what is a UAPTF?
Unidentified Aerial Phenomena
Task Force.
It was developed by
the DOD and Naval Intelligence
to investigate
otherworldly threats.
Otherworldly threats.
Like, uh... Like aliens?
That's right.
The Superman appearance was just the latest
in a long line of mysterious incidents.
So Superman's an alien?
Yes. We believe he might be.
You're saying aliens are real?
It's worse than that, Major.
We believe they're already here.
♪ I am not a woman I'm a god ♪
♪ I am not a martyr
I'm a problem ♪
We have no idea what they want, or
what they're willing to do to get it,
so we have to assume they're
extremely dangerous and hostile.
♪ A couple bodies in the garden
Where the grass grows... ♪
Are you ready?
If there are aliens
in Port Oswego,
we will find them.
I'm ready to try.
♪ So I'll stay right here
'Cause I'm better all alone ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm better all alone
♪ I am not a woman I'm a god ♪
♪ I am not a martyr
I'm a problem ♪
♪ I am not a legend
I'm a fraud ♪
No splash.
♪ I am not a woman I'm a god ♪